A Guide to the Richmond Jaycees, 1936-2002
Library of Virginia
- Project Files, 1956-2002.
  - Brotherhood Week Program, 1967-1968. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo Shoot, 1971. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Byrd Movie Night, 2002. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Camp Virginia Sponsorship, 1982. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Camp Virginia Work Party, 2002. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Camperships for Camp Virginia, 1993. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Can Wars: Recycle for Camperships, 1990-1991. (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Canal Walk, 1986-1987. (Box 29, Folder 14-15)
  - Canal Walk, 1986-1987. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Candidates Forum, 1987. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Candidates Night, 1963. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Candidates Night, 1965. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Candidates Night, 1970. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Candidates Night (City Council), 1964. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Candidates Night (City Council), 1968. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Candidates Night (City Council), 1970. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Candidates Night (City Council), 1972. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Captains Choice Golf Tourney, 1982. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Career Planning, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Carols for the Elderly, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Casino Night, 1989-1990. (Box 30, Folder 13-14)
  - Casino Night, 1990-1991. (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
  - CEO Cabbies (a.k.a. Fortune 500 Forum), 1993-1994. (Box 31, Folder 3-4)
  - Celebrate Wellness, 1992. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Central Intercollegiate Athletic Association Convention Welcome Booth, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Cerebral Palsy Childrens Outing, 1968. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Cerebral Palsy Childrens Outing, 1970. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Cerebral Palsy Childrens Outing, 1971. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Chad Turner Fund, 1979-1981. (Box 32, Folder 4-8)
  - Chairmans Planning Guide Training, 1987. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Chairmans Planning Guide Training for the Board, 1990-1991. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Chapter Awards, 1967-1968. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Chapter Development, 1962-1963. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Chapter Development, 1963-1964. (Box 33, Folder 5-6)
  - Chapter Development, 1966-1967. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Chapter Development, 1966-1967. (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
  - Chapter Elections, 1967. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Chapter Elections Campaign Material, 1974-1986. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Chapter Management Entry, 1976-1977. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Chapter Management Entry, 1977-1978. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Chapter Management Programming, 1980-1981. (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
  - Chapter Management Programming, 1982-1983. (Box 35, Folder 3-4)
  - Chapter Management, 1983-1984. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Chapter Management, 1992-1993. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Chapter Management, 1992-1993. (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  - Chapter Management and Individual Development, 1971-1972. (Box 36, Folder 3-6)
  - Chapter Management and Individual Development, 1971-1972. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Chapter Management and Leadership Training, 1968-1969. (Box 37, Folder 2-4)
  - Chapter Management and Leadership Training, 1969-1970. (Box 37, Folder 5-6)
  - Chapter Phonebank, 1990-1991. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Chapter Survey, 1977-1978. (Box 38, Folder 2-6)
  - Chapter Survey, 1978-1988. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Chapter Survey, 1981. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Chapter Survey, 1987. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Chapter Survey, 1987. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Chapter Survey, 1989-1990. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Chapter Survey, 1990-1991. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Charter Night, 1975-1977. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Child Abuse, 1973-1974. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Child Watch, 1984. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Children's Theatre, 1985. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Caroling, 1985. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Caroling, 1987. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Pageant Ushers, 1959. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Parade, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 4-9)
  - Christmas Parade, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Parade, 1991. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Parade, 1991. (Box 41, Folder 3-5)
  - Christmas Parade, 1991. (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
  - Christmas Parade, 1992-1993. (Box 42, Folder 3-4)
  - Christmas Parade Charity Ball, 1987-1988. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Christmas Party, 1967-1968. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1976-1977. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1977-1978. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1978-1979. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1982-1983. (Box 43, Folder 2-3)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1984-1985. (Box 43, Folder 4-5)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1985. (Box 43, Folder 6-7)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1986. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1987. (Box 44, Folder 2-3)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1990. (Box 44, Folder 4-6)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1991. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1991. (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 1993. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Christmas Tree Sales, 2002. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Church Visitation, 1988. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Church Visitation, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - City Council Liaison Committee, 1971-1972. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - City Council Meeting and City Managers Meeting, 1962-1963. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - City Council Report, 1966. (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - City Council Visit, 1990. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - City Manager Meetings, 1960-1961. (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - City of Richmond Government Night, 1967. (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Clean Out Your Closet for the Homeless, 1990. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Clean Your Closets for the Homeless, 1991-1992. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Clean Your Closets for the Homeless, 1991-1992. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Clean Your Closets for the Homeless, 1991-1992. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Coat and Tie Recruitment, 1991. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Coat and Tie Recruitment, 1991-1992. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - College Football Game, 1992-1993. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Comedy Club, 1988. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Comedy for Muscular Dystrophy Association, 1986. (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Comedy for St. Jude's, 1987. (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Committee to Study Location for Bi-Monthly Meetings, 1973. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Community Ambassador Program, 1964-1965. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Community Development, 1964-1965. (Box 47, Folder 3-4)
  - Community Development Programming, 1985-1986. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Community Development Programming, 1989-1990. (Box 47, Folder 6-8)
  - Community Development Programming, 1989-1990. (Box 48, Folder 1-4)
  - Community Development Programming, 1990-1991. (Box 49, Folder 1-7)
  - Community Development Programming, 1990-1991. (Box 50, Folder 1-6)
  - Community Development Programming, 1990-1991. (Box 51, Folder 1-5)
  - Community Development Programming, 1990-1991. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Community Development Programming, 1991-1992. (Box 52, Folder 2-4)
  - Community Development Programming, 1992-1993. (Box 52, Folder 5-6)
  - Community Development Programming, 1992-1993. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Community Development Survey, 1961. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Community Development Survey, 1965-1966. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Community Fundraising, 1987-1988. (Box 53, Folder 4-7)
  - Community Fundraising, 1987-1988. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Community Fundraising, 1990-1991. (Box 54, Folder 2-5)
  - Community Fundraising, 1990-1991. (Box 54, Folder 6-7)
  - Community Health and Safety, 1959-1960. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Community Health and Safety, 1960-1961. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Community Involvement, 1971-1972. (Box 55, Folder 3-5)
  - Community Leadership Recognition, 1972-1973. (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
  - Community Leadership Recognition, 1972-1973. (Box 56, Folder 1-3)
  - Community Needs, 1990. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Community Needs Committee, 1991-1992. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Candidates Night (Third District Candidates), 1962. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Candidates Night, 1964. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Candidates Night, 1964. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Congressional Committee, 1965-1966. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Report, 1966. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Congressional Report, 1967-1968. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Congressional Visit, 1967. (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Consolidation Survey, 1967. (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Constitution Revision Referendum, 1970. (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Coed Volleyball Team, 1991-1992. (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Corporate Recruiting, 1989-1990. (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - CPR Training, 1978. (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - CPR Training, 1979. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - CPR Training, 1989. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Crestar Classic Concessions, 1989. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Crestar Classic Concessions, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Crime Against the Elderly, 1978-1979. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Crime Prevention for the Elderly, 1991-1992. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Crime Prevention for the Elderly, 1991-1992. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Darts Night, 1991. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Degree Program, 1991-1992. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Degrees of Jaycee, 1990-1991. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Delegate to Junior Chamber International XXII World Congress, 1967. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Dinner Meeting Announcement Sheets, 1989-1990. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Dinner Meeting Raffle, 1988-1989. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Dinner Meetings, 1991-1992. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - District III Competitions, 1991-1992. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - DMV Safety Belts, 1986. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Dribble and Shoot, 1969. (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Dribble and Shoot, 1969-1970. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Dribble and Shoot, 1985. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Dribble and Shoot, 1985-1986. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Dribble and Shoot, 1988. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Dribble and Shoot, 1989-1990. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Dribble and Shoot, 1992. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Drive for the Blind, 1990-1991. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Drive for the Blind, 1991-1992. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Drive for the Blind, 1991-1992. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Drive for the Blind, 1992-1993. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Duck Race on the James, 1991. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Duck Race on the James, 1991. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Ducks Unlimited Parking Fundraiser, 1985. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Earth Day at Maymont, 1991. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Easter Egg Hunt, 1960. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Easter Egg Hunt for Underprivileged Children, 1961. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Election Report, 1968. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Elections Committee, 1965. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Encore! Theatre Trip, 1990. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Conference, 1972. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Equal Rights Amendment Forum, 1975. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Extension of North Richmond Jaycees, 1964-1965. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Fall Competitions, 1993. (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Fall Speak-Up, 1987. (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Family Movie Night, 1991. (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Family Picnic, 1987. (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Fan Free Clinic Assistance Project, 1971. (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Faux Wedding Reception, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Feed the Homeless, 1991. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Filling Library Shelves Abroad, 1966. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Fingerprinting Children, 1989. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Fire Prevention Night, 1962. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Fireside Smoker, 1976-1977. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Fishing Rodeo, 1959. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Food for Russia, 1992. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Fourth of July Glow Necklace Blast, 2002. (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Free Films Project, 1969-1970. (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Gamble Hill Christmas Party, 1960. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - General Assembly Night, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - General Assembly Visit, 1991. (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - General Assembly Visitation, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1962. (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1963. (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1964. (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1965. (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1966. (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1967. (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1969. (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1970. (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1971. (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1972. (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1973. (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1976. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1979. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Get Out the Vote, 1980. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1944-1974. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1960-1961. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1962-1963. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1963-1964. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1965-1966. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1966-1967. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1967-1968. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1970-1971. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1972-1973. (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1972-1973. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1974-1975. (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1974-1975. (Box 63, Folder 1-3)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1975-1976. (Box 63, Folder 4-5)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1976-1977. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1980-1981. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1981-1982. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1982-1983. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1983-1984. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1986-1987. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1989-1990. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1990-1991. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1991-1992. (Box 64, Folder 9-10)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Award, 1991-1993. (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Notebook, 1992-1993. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Giessenbier Memorial Notebook, 1992-1993. (Box 65, Folder 4-5)
  - Glaucoma Screening, 1975. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Governmental Affairs Competition, 1964. (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Governmental Affairs Competition, 1965. (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Governmental Affairs Competition, 1967. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Governmental Affairs Competition, 1969-1970. (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Grand Illumination, 1992. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Great American Duck Race, 1990. (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Great James River Raft Race, 1976. (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Gubernatorial Candidates Night, 1965. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Gumball Machines, 1959-1975. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Gumball Machines, 1976-1990. (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Gumball Machines, 1976-1977. (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Gumball Machines, 1978-1979. (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Gumball Machine Placement, 1985. (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Half-Way House, 1970-1971. (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Half-Way House, 1971-1972. (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Half-Way House, 1971-1972. (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Halloween Ghost Tour for Muscular Dystrophy, 1989. (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Halloween Party, 1990-1991. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Halloween Party, 1991-1992. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Halloween Party for Underprivileged Children, 1960-1970. (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Haunted House Social, 1991. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Highway Safety, 1978. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Holiday Food Drive, 2002. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Holiday Social, 1991. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Holiday Social, 1991-1992. (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Host of Quarterly Work Conference, 1962. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Host of the Virginia State Convention, 1959-1960. (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Hosting Junior Chamber International Dignitaries, 1964. (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Hosting Foreign Visitors, 1964-1965. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Hosting State Outstanding Young Educator, 1965-1966. (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Hot Dog Night, 1960. (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - House of Delegates Candidates Night, 1973. (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Housing Winterization, 1976-1979. (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - How I Spent My T.O.Y.A. Vacation, 1991. (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - How to Buy/Sell a Home, 1989. (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - How to Recruit, 1987. (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - How to Start Your Own Business, 1989. (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Human and Environmental Improvement, 1969-1970. (Box 68, Folder 6-8)
  - Hunting and Firearm Safety Instruction, 1969. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Hunting and Firearm Safety Instruction, 1970. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Hunting and Firearm Safety Instruction, 1971. (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Ice Cream Social, 1986. (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Independence Hall Essay Contest, 1964-1968. (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Individual Development Day, 1988. (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Individual Development Day, 1991. (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Individual Development Day, 1991. (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Individual Development Day, 1991. (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Individual Development Day, 1992. (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Individual Development Notebook, 1975-1976. (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Individual Development Notebook, 1975-1976. (Box 70, Folder 1-4)
  - Individual Development Notebook, 1975-1976. (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
  - Individual Development, 1984-1985. (Box 71, Folder 3-4)
  - Individual Development Programming, 1985-1986. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Individual Development Programming, 1985-1986. (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
  - Individual Development Programming, 1989-1990. (Box 72, Folder 3-4)
  - Individual Development Programming, 1990-1991. (Box 72, Folder 5-6)
  - Individual Development Programming, 1991-1992. (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
  - Individual Development Programming, 1992-1993. (Box 73, Folder 3-5)
  - Individual Development Programming, 1992-1993. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Indoor Horse Racing at Virginia State Fair, 1994. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Tours, 1959-1960. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Inner City Small Business Assistance, 1969-1970. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Internal Affairs, 1959-1960. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Internal Affairs, 1960-1961. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Internal Affairs, 1961-1962. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - International Center Survey, 1965. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - International Dinners, 1964. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - International Food Festival, 1987. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - International Food Festival, 1989. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - International Goodwill, 1967. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - International Memberships, 1963. (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - International Night, 1961. (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - International Night, 1962. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - International Night, 1963. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - International Night, 1964. (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - International Night, 1965. (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - International Night, 1966. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - International Night, 1967. (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - International Night, 1968. (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - International Night, 1972. (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - International Relations, 1960-1961. (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Investigation of Virginia General Assembly, 1966-1967. (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - James River Clean-Up, 1987. (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - James River Park Clean-Up, 1989. (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - James River Park Improvement, 1990-1991. (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - James River Raft Race and Raise the Rafters Night, 1976-1978. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - James River Rafting Trip, 1992. (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - James River Steps, 1986. (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Jaybill, 1975-1976. (Box 76, Folder 7-8)
  - Jaybill, 1991-1992. (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Jaybill, 1991-1992. (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Jaybill, 1992-1993. (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Jaynote, 1991-1992. (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Jaycee Night at the Ball Game, 1967. (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Jaycee Week, 1984-1985. (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Jaycee Week, 1987-1988. (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Jaycee Week, 1989. (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Jaycee Week, 1991. (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Jaycee Week, 1992-1993. (Box 78, Folder 2-4)
  - Jaycees in Miniature Exposition, 1960. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Jaycees in Miniature Exposition, 1961. (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Jaynote, 1990-1991. (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Jobs Fair, 1991. (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Jobs Fair, 1991. (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - June Jubilee, 1976-1977. (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - June Jubilee, 1978-1980. (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Junior Bowling Tournament, 1962-1963. (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Junior Bowling Tournament, 1974. (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Junior Champ Track and Field Development Program, 1968. (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Junior Champ Track and Field Meet, 1969. (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Junior Champ Track Competition, 1970. (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Junior Champ Track Competition, 1971. (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Junior Champ Track Meet, 1970-1975. (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Junior Citizenship Award, 1962. (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Junior Citizenship Award, 1963. (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Junior Fishing Tournament, 1967. (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Junior Fishing Tournament, 1969. (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Junior Golf Tournament, 1959. (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Junior Golf Tournament, 1962. (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Junior Golf Tournament, 1963. (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Junior Golf Tournament, 1965. (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Junior Golf Tournament, 1968. (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Junior Golf Tournament, 1969. (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Junior Golf Tournament, 1970. (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Junior Golf Tournament, 1972. (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Junior Golf Tournament, 1974. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Kentucky Derby Party, 1993. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Kickoff Meeting, 1971-1972. (Box 80)
  - Kick Off the Month Happy Hour, 1992-1993. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Kids to Camp, 1987. (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Kids to Camp, 1987. (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Labor Day Coffee Break, 1961. (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Labor Day Coffee Break, 1962. (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Labor Day Coffee Break, 1963. (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Laugh it Up for Muscular Dystrophy Association, 1987-1988. (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Laugh it Up for the Muscular Dystrophy Association, 1987-1988. (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Leadership Development, 1985-1986. (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Advisory Committee, 1955-1956. (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Liberty and Libation for All, 1991. (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Lt. Governor and Attorney General Candidates Night, 1973. (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Lieutenant Governors Candidates Night, 1971. (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Liquor by the Drink Forum, 1967. (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Little League Baseball, 1970. (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1979. (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1980. (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1981. (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1982. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1983. (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1985. (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1986. (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1987. (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1987-1988. (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1989. (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1991. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1992-1993. (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1994. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, 1996-1997. (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Little Santa Shopping Tour, 1959. (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Little Santa Shopping Tour, 1962. (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Little Santa Shopping Tour, 1967. (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Little Santa Shopping Tour, 1971. (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Little Santa Shopping Tour, 1974. (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Little Santa Shopping Tour, 1975. (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Little Santa Shopping Tour, 1976. (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Little Santa Shopping Tour, 1977. (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Little Santa Shopping Tour, 1978. (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Local Government Debates, 1963-1964. (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Local Personal Property Tax Reform, 1963-1964. (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Lock It and Pocket the Key, 1972. (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Lock It and Pocket the Key, 1973. (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Locket It and Pocket the Key, 1973. (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Lock It and Pocket the Key, 1976-1977. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1992-1993. (Box 83, Folder 4)